http://www.fundscrip.com/privacy

1. Privacy
FundScrip (commonly referred to as “we,” “us,” “FundScrip,” and together with its parent company Fundstream Inc.) is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of FundScrip’s information handling practices when you use the services located at fundscrip.com, as well as the Group Administration Site, the Supporter Ordering Site, and any other website located on this domain and related subdomains (“the Platform”) (collectively, the “Services”).
2. Information Collection
Information which includes but is not limited to, your name, group name, email address, phone number, address, financial information (e.g. credit card information) or other information we may receive relating to communications you send us is considered personal information (the “Personal Information”). You may be asked to provide Personal Information when you use the Platform, register as a supporter or group administrator, or use the Services.
During the normal course of your use of the Services, we may collect additional Personal Information for the purpose of providing the Services, and may include information relating to processing transactions, order fulfillment, customer service, or other information.
Traffic Logging
In addition, when you interact with or use the Services, FundScrip automatically collects certain data which is not confidential in nature and may include your internet protocol (IP) address, date and time of access, web page(s) visited, language use, browser type, internet service provider, and computer operating system.
Cookies and Related Technologies
Cookies are small data files that are sent and stored on your computer when you visit certain websites, and are primarily used to track a user’s preferences and use of a website. FundScrip uses cookies for a variety of purposes. One important use of cookies is to help identify you while you are logged in to the Platform. Consequently, if your browser does not accept cookies, you will be unable to join or login to our program through the Platform. You will, however, be able to browse our website as a visitor. The information FundScrip collects from cookies and web server logs is used to administer and customize information you receive when visiting our Platform. FundScrip may also use and share aggregate information from cookies and web server logs to analyze and improve the Services. This information does not identify individual visitors or customers.
FundScrip may also use related technologies including web beacons, tracking pixels, and tokens in order to facilitate your use of the Services.
Google Analytics
FundScrip uses a service provided by Google called Google Analytics. This service allows FundScrip to analyze how people find us on the internet, as well as how our Platform is used, so that FundScrip can better understand the needs of users and improve the Services accordingly.
Advertising and Remarketing
FundScrip uses online advertising services provided by third parties who collect data, usually in the form of a unique numerical identifier, using cookies or other methods. This data is used to display customized advertising to people who have previously visited the FundScrip Platform. This type of advertising is called “remarketing”. Because of the interconnected nature of online advertising industry, these remarketing advertisements may be served by a variety of third parties.
You may opt out of remarketing advertisements, and other personalized advertisements by participating companies here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
3. Purpose and Use
FundScrip collects Personal Information in order to:
Identify you when you login or place orders
Enable us to provide the Services to you
Share information with relevant partners in order to provide the Services to you (e.g. shipping companies)
Contact you about your account or to provide you with support
Analyze how people use the Services in order to make improvements
Share aggregated, non-identifiable statistics with our participating retailers and other partners
Investigate all activities and actions that we believe may contravene the terms of use of the Services.
4. Information Sharing and Disclosure
Except as detailed in in this Privacy Policy, FundScrip does not share Personal Information with third parties.
In order to provide the Services to you, FundScrip may share some information with third parties. Some of the circumstances where we may need to share information are as follows:
Payment Processing / Transactions
FundScrip may share relevant information such as your financial information (e.g. credit card information) and billing information to third parties for the purpose of payment processing and related functions.
Order Fulfillment
FundScrip may share relevant information such as your mailing address with shipping companies.
Email Services
FundScrip may share relevant information such as your email address with third party email service providers for the purpose of sending emails.
Legal Requests, Fraud & Obligations
FundScrip may disclose Personal Information about you to third parties when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena or search warrant, or in the course of legal proceedings. We may also disclose Personal Information as we believe appropriate to enforce or apply our rights under our agreements with customers, to protect the rights, property or safety of FundScrip, our customers and others, including exchanging information for fraud protection and credit risk reduction, to enforce our policies, and to respond to claims regarding the violation of the rights of others or protect anyone’s rights, property or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.
Business Transfers
FundScrip may also share Personal Information with its affiliates, service providers, or organizations involved in any possible merger with, or acquisition of FundScrip. We will notify you via prominent notice on the FundScrip Platform for 30 days prior to such a change of ownership or control of your Personal Information, or prior to the implementation of any material change in this statement or our information-handling practices as described in this statement.
If we ever make the decision to share customer Personal Information with third parties for reasons other than those indicated in this Privacy Policy, we will notify you ahead of time, and we will not share your information without your consent.
5. Accessing or Modifying Your Information
You may contact us at any time to inquire about your Personal Information that is held by FundScrip.
You can ask us to update, correct, or provide you with a copy of your Personal Information. Where relevant, you may also ask us to delete that information. Please note that certain information may be retained by FundScrip for a period of time that is necessary for our legitimate business purposes, or where required by law.
6. Information Security and Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS)
FundScrip uses industry-recognized safeguards that meet federal standards for the protection of your Personal Information, including but not limited to: monitoring for intrusion attempts; SSL (Secure Socket Layer), data and password encryption technology; firewalls and systems monitoring; and security audits and inspections. Only authorized employees have access to Personal Information.
FundScrip is in full compliance with all requirements of the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS).
7. Protection of Children
FundScrip’s services are not intended for persons under the age of eighteen (18) (or the lawful age in their respective jurisdiction). If FundScrip becomes aware that a minor has submitted personal information, FundScrip will reject said submission and will take such steps to remove such information from its records.
8. Legal Disclaimer
FundScrip provides the Services on an “AS-IS” and “AS-AVAILABLE” basis, without liability of any kind. FundScrip shall not be responsible for events beyond its direct control. Due to the complex and constantly changing nature of technology, FundScrip neither guarantees nor represents that there will be error-free performance regarding the privacy of a user’s Personal Information, and it will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Personal Information.
9. Email Preferences
FundScrip uses email as the primary method for which we contact you. FundScrip allows you to manage your email preferences, where you may opt-out of receiving certain email messages. Please note that by joining the FundScrip program, we may send you email messages that are critical to your participation.
10. General
FundScrip may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we materially change this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices we will notify you by email and/or through a notice on our web site prior to their implementation. FundScrip recommends that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly.
11. Contact FundScrip
To contact FundScrip about this Privacy Policy please email privacy@fundscrip.com or mail us at:
Fundstream Inc.
1441 Carrie-Derrick St
Montreal, Quebec H3C 4S9
This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 27, 2020.
